If I get your card,
I put it right in the middle of the deck and I just make a yellow pass.
One,
two,
three.
Do you know what I did?
Nothing
That I burst into your letter,
disappears from the deck and appears inside my hat.
Inside my hat You can see,
My God,
show it to the camera.
How did you do that?
Robson in the middle of the deck.
And now I'm going to make a mandatory pass again.
One,
two Now slow down,
Darn it,
what a crazy mess.
Our bro three Slashes his finger and has skill with his fingers,
huh?
Your letter No,
it's not going,
It's back in the hat you've already emptied the hat,
man,
it's not possible Next to my hat.
What angle is it?
Imagined if I do this Slow motion,
let's see what happens.
Nani,
I do a tight knee pass,
tight grip Ha ha Opa.
I think I got too tight.
Nani,
sorry.
It seems that now the deck,
the deck that was in your crazy hand,
and the whole deck is gone.
Oh, no,
no, no,
no Inside my hat I stopped bro?
Saved from palms to fall in the world.
What a disgrace.